

ELDAR GAZIZOV

Python Software Engineer

Contact Information

+ 420 777 442 357 Tel:

Email: kursus1010@gmail.com

Location: Czech Republic, Prague

linkedin.com/in/eldar-gazizov/ Linkedin:

Website: bigbossguru.github.io/MyWebsitePortfolio/

GitHub: github.com/bigbossguru

Profile

I'm a Python Software Developer with three years of experience. I have extensive experience in web development (backend), data analysis, processing, and calculation, writing scripts to automate various processes.

I have experience in designing database models using PostgreSQL relational databases and non-relational MongoDB. And I use Docker to deploy applications and various services.

At the same time, I'm studying javascript and the popular ReactJS frontend library. I have a good base and understanding of work.

Main Skills

Languages

Python Russian

Czech Advanced PostgreSQL

Native

English Advanced MongoDB

■ Django REST Framework

JavaScript

React

Employment

Senior Software Engineer

AKKA Czech Republic s.r.o.

Apr 2022 — Present

Prague

Web development (backend), analysis, processing, and calculation of data, writing scripts to automate various processes.

Software Engineer

AKKA Czech Republic s.r.o.

Dec 2021 — Apr 2022

Prague

Web development (backend), analysis, processing, and calculation of data, writing scripts to automate various processes.

Software Developer

Elektroline a.s

Feb 2020 — Dec 2021

Prague

Development of visualization for HMI panels. Development software for automate configure industrial router and servers

PLC Programmer

Elektroline a.s

Feb 2020 — Dec 2021

Prague

Design and implementation of automatic control systems, testing SW on the installation.

Education

Czech Technical University of Prague

Sep 2014 — May 2018

Bachelor of Information and automation technology